GIORGOS IOANNIDIS

House 56, Room 9, Level 0 University Court University of Surrey Guildford GU2-7IN mobile:07568 381143 email: gi00013@surrey.ac.uk

Personal details

Summary

- Very good knowledge of Greek and English language
- Average business experience
- Completed military service

Skills and achievements

Leadership

Able to work well using own initiative but also lead and convince teammates as during my military service I was an officer.

Teamwork

Enjoy being part of a team as it improves communication skills, which I find very helpful.

Problem solving

Able to find solutions quickly and effectively to resolve problems, experience which I gained from my military service.

Responsibilities

Mature enough to welcome and undertake all responsibilities, which are brought before me and handle them in the best possible means in favor of my clients, company and colleagues.

Honor

I am obliged to work legally and ethically, without any acts at the expense of my colleagues and my company.

Language abilities

My mother language is Greek but I speak English fluently.

Education and Qualifications

2012- present Studying computers science at University of

Surrey

2009-2012 St. John Lyceum Limassol

(Equivalent with GCE A-level)

2006-2009 St. John Elementary school Limassol

(Equivalent with GCSE)

Work Experience

2011 (June-August) I & C The PC Connection

• Computer Technician

2010 (June-August) I & C The PC Connection

• Computer Technician

2009 (June-August) I & C The PC Connection

• Computer Technician

Voluntary experience:

2009-present Blood-donor.

2007-2009 Various music concerts for charity.

Interests:

Playing the guitar. Watching sports.

Travelling.

Triumph Motorcycles Ltd Normandy Way Hinckley Leicestershire LE10 3BZ United Kingdom House 56, Level 0, Room 9
University Court
University of Surrey
Guildford
GU2-7JN
United Kingdom

URL in PTY database: https://secure.eps.surrey.ac.uk/secure-cgi/placement/ptdetail.pl?det=5356

02 January 2013

Dear Sir / Madame

Manufacturing

I am writing to apply for the above position as advertised on the placement database at the University of surrey.

I am very interested in your line of business as I feel it will be very challenging for me and it will give me the opportunity in working as part of a team, due to the fact I completed my military service as an officer, I realize the importance of people interacting with each other on various assignments.

My CV shows my previous experience as a Technician in a computer company where I gained practical knowledge and experience where my work was highly praised by my employers (references can be forwarded).

I would be pleased to be given the opportunity in having a meeting with you for a further interview.

Yours sincerely,

Giorgos Ioannidis.